maybe I can signal to somebody for some
help but he stood right by me because he
knew like that's of course what I wanted
to do was to get some
help what's going on folks this is Ryan
Perez with go live and prosper uh
courtesy of or powered by hustle Zone TV
and um we are also this is also brought
to you by uh Bai creative that's my
marketing agency we websites um branding
logo design and everything under the sun
just hit me up uh go to our website uh
ww. boty creative.com and that's
ww.bbc creative with a so I'm just G to
wait for um everyone to come into the
room I'm going to share this out and
make sure folks uh to share out this
broadcast because you know I I have a
really good guest uh today
on the hustle Zone hold on one second
just every time I hear my voice I sound
like Kermit the Frog so anyway we're
gonna we're gonna we're gonna send this
out um just sending it out to all my
groups live stream and of course this
broadcast is a recording it's a taping
um you can find uh once the the
interview is done you'll be be able to
find this interview on all you know
major streaming platforms Apple music uh
uh Stitch Google podcast and um and
Spotify so um anyway let's let's get to
our Our Guest uh so she is a single
mother of three kids she's worked three
jobs she also trains for the Olympics
six times a week for Speed skating on
ice for a short track she she is one of
three of the only black women in the
world okay let me repeat that again she
is one of three of the only black women
in the world competing in her category
uh when she say black women can do it
all this is what they sorry when they
say that black women can do it all this
is what they what they meant and I just
want you guys to give it up for
Lear how's it
going can you can you hear
me okay now I can hear your
voice there seems to be um an audio uh
seems to seems to be some audio problems
there but um let's just do a mic test
this will be all edited out once we uh
uh once I put it on the podcast can you
do a mic test for
me hello hello hello hello hello awesome
awesome awesome so how are you doing H
how has it
been I'm good I'm good how are you I'm
I'm doing amazing I'm doing amazing that
we we actually because we've been
planning to do this podcast for for
quite some time actually last year and
um I met you right I met you on uh on
Instagram out of all things uh we we we
posted about your story because we saw
was phenomenal and you were the video
the video that you that that we saw of
you you were running like uh uh like the
Road Runner like you are an
amazing you are amazing athlete like you
have the stand you have stamina out of
this world like like how like how how is
it how how often do you
train uh six days a week sometimes two
to four times a day sometimes oh my God
it always depends on what have to what I
have to do exctly and then now I'm uh
dual sport I do track cycling now
so okay um hold on one second what did
you say
okay see you
later okay sorry about that is my son
he's going but anyway so uh we have uh
we have a question at the hustle Zone
and um normally the way we start every
hustle Zone we've been doing this for
three years and the the number one
question we ask what is your story so
you pretty much have the you have the
the platform now to tell us from the
very beginning what is your story how
did you to this point in your
life um Run field and I crossed
over I guess you say from that sport or
completely leaving it after I went
through
abuse and I didn't really want anything
else to do with track because of that
because um I had went through a very bad
domestic violence
situation and uh kidnapped with
My Two children in the back seat was
missing for three months and I was
beaten like every single day for three
months straight uh near death ex you
know beatings and um just went a lot
with that and so I just kind of was like
I don't want to do that
anymore so if you fast forward I um was
skating in a regular skating ring and
then after it over so many people kind
of like bomb rushed me so to speak and
they're like who are you and I'm like
what and they're like nobody skates that
fast like why are you in a a regular
roll ring skating like something's wrong
with you like uh I'm like huh I'm like
no I'm just you know train they're like
oh we believe you so basically after I
left left and you know people want to
take pictures of me I'm like kind of
about that so then fast forward again I
see the
Oly speak oh my gosh
what so Beau and what was said to me
about my skating and then that and just
kind of you know got involved with
that after
that so um let's let's dial it back a
little bit
you you were track and field like how
long have you were you running
track uh
since um uh like kind of like since I
say nth grade I think yeah since ninth
grade and why did you figure that that
was something that you wanted to do and
that you had um talent in
that um oh when I ran track
yeah it just it was like really fun for
me and I U just liked
running um and all my light people
always say oh you should run track like
I just and then I just kind of finally
got in involved in like Middle
School yeah and do you do you think you
were competitive at the time like were
you were you top in your in in your
category or like how how um give me a a
a synopsis of you know what type of uh
track star I wouldn't say I was top in
tracking field no um but I was really
good on the I guess the relays so where
they put me at anchor on the
4x4 um and then I was like uh I was
third leg on the
4x1 very good at like the mile um I was
good at that um like I ran like my best
was like
455 uh where I got like third place in
something called a road Mouse
championships where they had to like
close the street down and stuff so that
was pretty
cool that's pretty awesome and when um
and then you said that you were in a
abusive relationship and and that's why
you stopped doing
track yeah because I was I was running
track um when that end up happening to
me so I just kind of didn't want to do
that sport anymore because of that and
like when you say abusive relationship
was it more of a you know was it mental
abuse was it physical abuse AB was it
both um you know uh it was definitely
all forms of abuse mostly uh
physical wow it was very mental
psychological verbal but very very very
physical I mean
blood uh blacks black
eye uh my nose kind of bit off um bit
into my vein where I thought I was going
to die
because my whole arm turned turned a
different color he bit into my arm like
like a dog it was it was
awful oh my God and I'm sorry I'm sorry
to to hear that and did you like at the
time and you don't have to answer this
but like at the time did you know what
you were getting yourself into did you
have past abuse and and kind of followed
the you know the pattern of because you
know some people have said that you know
what people that have been in abusive
situations kind of walk into
relationships that are kind of or kind
of grew up in relationship or sorry grew
up in abusive environments and then they
kind of you know um they go on to follow
that that path uh did you grow up in in
an abusive
environment uh no actually that was my
first abusive
relationship wow so um and then so at
that time you uh and then you you said
after the abuse then you got k
kidnapped it was yeah well it's the same
person because I wanted to get out of
the relationship CU I was tired of being
abused every single day and I was like I
can't do this anymore like I I don't
want to be your punching bag and then
next you know there a knife to my throat
and I'm kidnapped with my two children
in the back seat with a knife to my
throat making me drive 18 hours away
somewhere I've never been in my
life Wow and then you you had to endure
that for three
years or not three years three months
three months and you you didn't know
where you
were you had no clue where you were or
like how did you like you how did that
happen how did that take
place um like I said he had knif to my
throat um while I was driving yeah and
uh he forced me to drive the 18 M or
excuse me 18 hours away and then uh I
understand a lot of people have
questions because it sounds kind like
okay it's a knife it's not a gun I'm
like but you don't understand it's
different like when
it's right when it's happened and also
we did people always question about
getting stopping for gas and everything
and so many different things went
through my head like I was like I could
run I could outrun him actually because
we um he he know was at the track with
me some time trying to help me work out
so to speak and actually shockingly was
faster than him but
um he took my he took my keys and he
took my phone so he had my phone the
whole time and then my children all I
could think about was them I'm like even
if I go run away what about my children
what's gonna happen to them so that's
another reason why I couldn't just run
and then also when I would uh when he
stop for gas like I said he always have
my took the keys and my phone but then
also uh he would walk with me to the
restroom like usually I would stop and
it's like only one stall so he's
standing right outside the door and then
I'm trying to think maybe I can signal
to somebody for some help but he stood
right by me because he knew like that's
of course what I wanted to do was to get
some
help and I think about my children right
because if you
ran I don't want to jeopardize I was
like I just don't want to jeopardize
their life what if it goes to try to
kill them so I'm like I just have to
kind of take
it and how did you eventually break out
of that situation because obviously it
lasted for only three months like how
did
you um
actually we where we were it was
actually his friend's house and one day
he left and went to the store and friend
was like okay look what is going on he
told us you guys are here on vacation
and I don't really buy that because
you've been wearing the same outfit
every single day and nobody on vacation
wears the same outfit and also I just
want to let you know my daughter
saw and told us that she saw you getting
beat in the bathroom because the door
was not closed I'm like oh my gosh um so
at that point I broke down in tears and
I'm like well your friend is not really
who he says he is he kidnapped me my
children and forced me against my will
here I were not on vacation actually uh
he told me he was going to kill me if I
say
anything and um I don't even know where
we at where are we and they tell me oh
you're um in Texas this is Texas I'm
like wow I've never been here before um
and then they make some phone calls and
then they talk to the mother-in-law and
like okay we got to call the police and
I'm you know just scared out my mind
like he said if I tell anybody's going
to kill me or like well what if he like
what if he kills somebody now then what
somebody you need some help we got to
get you help and then that's how I kind
of got the police
involved wow and so the police came and
you know is he still in prison like what
what's this the status on him actually
he got out and then right after it was
over with me he ended up kidnapping
another lady it was very strange this
the same exact way kidnapped her and her
daughter kid kidnapped her at knife
Point um because some people contacted
me and C was crying to me I'm like uh
hello like what's going on because and
these are the same people who did not
believe my story and they're like we
know you do not know this woman and we
owe you a big apology because we thought
this man was a man of God like he
profess to love God and be a preacher
and all this stuff and um and you don't
know this lady and he kidnapped he just
kidnapped her and there's a big police
report and everything and he went to
jail or whatever behind her so he want
to apologize to you and I'm like oh my
gosh because nobody believed me like at
all of the story just sounded too
fake basic again someone else how did
you feel towards them were you did you
have animosity towards
them uh I I was no not an is very broken
very hurt because I'm like who sits
makes up a story like this who
I don't know anybody who does this why
would I there lie um it was hard time
because I'm heing abuse and then when I
finally come out and tell people they
don't believe me
really and then I just then I start
thinking about other people who are Abus
I'm like now I see why people don't
really talk about it or they hide it for
many years and then talk about it
later because it just takes time to you
know work up the courage and you know
just not pretty much not give an f um
you know just to say it because like you
know there's a lot of people that have
been in really bad situations and
there's a lot of you know people don't
really understand it's like when you're
an abusive relationship you can't just
leave you have to plan you have to plan
a way out because there's things at
stake like your money's at stake you
know you may have children at stake and
and whatnot and then there's people like
there's networks like maybe this
person's below maybe everyone just likes
that abusive person so sometimes you
have to be able
welled wow
exactly it's hard for people to believe
because they're like oh my gosh he's so
nice he always talks about the Bible
teaches the Bible and I'm like oh you
guys have no
idea yeah that's that's insane that's
insane so um how did you recover
mentally like you know what type of
self-care did you take um after that all
went
down um I had to be
therapy and
um a a lot of it took a long time
actually a lot of a lot of crying I went
through the depression I went through
everything you could think of but
thankfully I never turned to substance
abuse which I know a lot of people do um
because I don't drink I never smoke
never did drugs anything like that which
I'm very grateful before I just kind of
cried out to the most high God basically
and prayed all the time to for healing
and help um that's basically how I kind
of coped with
that and then what led you
into uh you know to this next phase in
your life because you know going on to
your
Instagram um you are a phenomenal
athlete
and you know like I could see like you
you put in like every every bit of
energy that you have in into what you're
doing now so how did you know so kind of
give me more an in-depth understanding
of that
transition uh the transition from
recovering to uh from recovering to now
you know running to compete in the the
Olympics
okay
um well it's just I I know I had goals
and dreams
before this the abuse happened to me and
I'm just like okay I don't want to do
track so what can I do um I just kind of
just thought about the the like
different sports I'm like oh I don't
like this I'm not gonna be passionate
about this and then like I said they all
came together the whole and that that
time at the skating rink and everybody's
coming up to me and I'm like well maybe
I'm good at this or something cuz why is
they acting this
way um and then I know some people even
accuse me of being a roller derby person
and I didn't even know what that was
until I looked it up and I was like oh
gosh no I would be skating and fighting
people ping people I was like I don't
want to do that so um so yeah it just uh
I had a love for skating and just kind
of going fast so to speak and then like
I said I thought it was beautiful when I
saw the speed skating on TV and I was
like I just have to get involved this is
amazing it's
beautiful and then you know and then the
rest is the rest is history so uh you
like I think
that when people saw you
skating was that something that was like
you know cuz obviously you had a gift
then but what made you so fast like was
it just that you've you know muscle
memory or you know what was the the
because obviously you're an outlier
people notice the difference so you know
what made you special at that
time um I guess I always take like if
it's anything to do with Athletics I
guess I always just go hard even if it's
you're just supposed to be having fun I
guess always shoot
sorry sorry about that go ahead so you
uh what were you saying oh yeah sorry
what made you special what
um uh what like what was it that that uh
how why did people notice you because
obviously you were faster but you know
what made you faster was it your was it
just something that was genetic or was
it something that um it was was it your
perseverance I think a bit of a bit of
both cuz uh my grandfather he passed
away at uh basically two weeks before he
turned
96 and all the way up until then he did
like 50 push-ups every day every morning
and did his little five pound weights
and stuff uh so I'm like wow that's
pretty insane to be 95 or 90 anything
and doing 50 push-ups every morning you
know he was pretty healthy uh but uh
yeah and then I just everything I I
guess I do with when it comes to
Athletics even if it's like uh supposed
to be fun I take it as a just go hard
like and I have goals and I don't
have situations like everybody else like
nothing's really given to me I have to
like work for
everything and I don't have like you
know peopley alone and the things I do
so I just kind of go hard and just sewn
out I guess you could say in focus and
just kind of like blank my mind and just
is work really hard even though I'm not
necessarily trying to let per se beat
some in my own Zone and then it just
kind of turns out that way if that makes
sense like I wasn't trying to be off
fting and then it just happened then
people are like who are you what is
going
on because I would always think that
like you know if you've been through all
of that atic event that you would be
using you know you know speed skating as
an
outlet you know just to release and to
release the pain from the past but was
it like that in this case or it was just
your just the fact that you were able to
zone out and
focus uh probably the zone out in focus
and the I guess the thought of not
having much and I'm like this is my my
one
opportunity like em said you got one
shot you know
um and just got for so it's kind of like
that and what made you now want to
compete in the Olympics like what was
the um because yeah obviously you saw it
on TV but like when did you make that
decision that hey um I'm gonna compete
and I'm gonna be the only black one of
the only black women to compete in this
category and um you know because like a
lot of people wouldn't wouldn't do that
they wouldn't think that but what what
gave you the motivation to do
it um well like I said I when I saw it
was so beautiful I'm like man I was like
I don't know how I'm G get into this but
I have to and then I just kind of found
out after the fact that it wasn't no
black really black people at all and I'm
like
whoa this is tight like I'm like okay
let's go make some history here um and
then to find out it's only three of us
in the world that do this uh for short
track I'm was like they're black I'm
like that's freaking cool like wow
that's
rare you know so very cool because like
I said it did kind of happen that way it
just happened that way like it wasn't
like someone hit you in the head and
then or you know something you know you
you tripped and you're like oh I'm gonna
do speed skate you just like you know
this is gonna be cool I think it's
beautiful yep that was pretty much
it and um you know and you've gotten a
lot of attention I mean you know like
your story has gone viral obviously a
lot of times it's gone viral on on on my
page um and I think we reposted or we
did we put more um of your content on
our page and those things went viral and
you have like Dame Dash following
you so how like do you know do you know
him personally or is he just following
you because he just likes the way you
grind I know I met him personally um
actually and he told me um to be my own
superhero and he just told me to go get
it like he's very straightforward
um he said be my be your own superhero
don't wait for nobody just go get it and
I was just like wow we gotta go we gotta
go get this I gotta go do this and like
you know just kind of like nobody cares
until you get there and I'm like I see
that because it's like people don't
really support you but then all of a
sudden when you have I don't know a ward
or whatever then they're like oh my gosh
I know her and it's like really you
weren't even there or supportive in the
process kind of thing you know yeah for
sure for sure well I I kind of feel the
same way and I was just I was live um I
did a little um audio podcast today and
I was just talking about how I don't
make content for my friends because had
I made content for my friends I would
probably not where I wanted to be
because you can't expect people to like
what you're doing and you can't expect
people to follow you you just have to
you know your you you like you know your
direction it's not to appease your
friends it's you know to get that end
goal it's to um it's to it's it's to
succeed to at whatever you're you're
you're trying to you know accomplish so
uh do you ever have you ever had any
people um discour you from going after
this oh my gosh every single day oh my
goodness I have so many people that's
more negative about this than positive
and they say the worst and I literally
have to say these exact words I do not
receive it sometimes I say return to
sinder um but a lot of time I say I do
not receive this because a lot of times
we receive things in our minds and our
spirits and hearts whatever Without
Really knowing it and then things start
happening it's like oh my go that person
is focused into my life and I I I'm
doing what they said like you know kind
of thing and I just try to be very
careful to
not uh feed off of that because I
understand a lot of times people project
what they feel that they can't do on to
you or what they may not be strong
enough to do or if they don't have the
courage or if they didn't go up there
their dreams they'll tell you that you
can't do it and there's a lot of people
are like really like jealous and just
really mean and evil for no reason at
all and it's like look I'm over a single
mother of three I'm trying to get there
you got a whole beautiful life already
made and you're coming me so mean and
foul and it's like for what you know
yeah for sure and I I totally understand
that because you know know when people
see you in the Limelight uh doing what
you're doing and you're focused you know
they and you know looks like you don't
got any problems they want to add
problems they just want to see something
happen oh my goodness like you have no
idea what I like what I deal with I'm
like oh my God you know people are just
they're crazy like I guess I get a lot
more negative and they hope I die and
you know just all kind of things I'm
like what is like is crazy sorry you you
had people say that they hope you die
from what and where and why like where
did that come from just like on
Instagram because of the whole you know
being only uh like I said the three
three of us that are black in the whole
world and then and then a lot of people
have a problem with that like so many
even black people they have a problem
with that whole oh why you got to focus
on being black and I'm like well first
of all I I didn't write it but I it is
something cool I think to
um necessarily focus on but to bring up
because it's rare and it's not like it's
something every day that people are
doing a lot of people that are you know
of our skin color don't like cold they
don't or don't like swimming or you know
or don't you don't see like black divers
or different things like that in
different sports so it's cool to I guess
you say recognize that for any sport not
just m
but it's it's just cool and exciting
because like oh my gosh if that person
could do it me too you know kind of like
that but people go off and you know
start putting you down and stuff oh
you're doing too much they don't take
all that why can't it just be like a
people I just have to be the black
mother yeah no I I hear you I hear you
and it's like you got to Zone it out
because like it's uh um it just I always
say that friends are not your fans and
fans are not your friends friends will
keep it to themselves but they will
support and whatnot and they won't be
honest with you but I find that fans are
the most they are highly reactive
because they will give you the most
praise but they'll also do the same when
you do something wrong like if you were
um you know you wore the wrong Nikes you
know what I mean like they're going to
be just as and that's great because like
I started when I was in I was doing um
YouTube videos back in the days like
probably 2009 and um a lot of the stuff
that I was doing I was trying to be
funny uh I got a lot of views it went
viral and then people are like and we
this and we that hope you die hope you
this and hope you that and you're
sitting there and I didn't want to look
at the comments I was like oh my God
like I can't I can't see this but you
know when I I got approved for for
monetization and I started making money
I'm like call me whatever you
want just you know keep on watching the
videos because like at least you're a
fan at least you you are you know
consuming the content so you know it
just comes with after a while it just
comes with the territory and the more
bigger you get the more scrutiny that
you get because look at old Oprah and
Gail even though I don't
agree even though I don't agree I just
you know you know there's just a lot of
scrutiny because when you think about it
um as much as I don't like what Gail did
I think that um I think that when we
look at things in retrospect we look at
Oprah you you know she may not be for
black men maybe she has a hidden agenda
um or whatever but the fact that she is
employing a lot of black people you know
she is putting a lot of black um men and
women through school and these are the
things that we don't talk about so it's
like yeah
you know when you are in the Limelight
you are you know you are open to get
scrutinized that just comes with the
territory right you you know what I mean
so but anyway um I guess uh the two
questions that I have for you if you
were to look back at your former
self what would you tell that
person uh
I was saying do not get married at
18 because I got married when I was 18
years old and end up having um two
children out of the marriage and then I
end up divorcing him six years later um
just just focus because you can get you
know you can get married and have love
later but of course most young people
they don't listen and they have to learn
the hard way like I did um and just stop
I guess searching for love love and just
really focus on uh building you know a
life for yourself as far as you know
becoming stable or having maybe a
business or having your own place your
own car those different Necessities you
need as an adult um when you transition
from you know teenagers to the adult
years that's definitely what I would say
and what would you say to young women
you know in general what would be your
number one advice for young women
besides what you would tell your for
myself uh I guess it'll still be
connected to that don't rush into
relationships with a man um are going to
be there um first like love yourself I
know it's very very cliche and people
like oh but it really matters so you can
get build self-esteem and uh like really
encourage yourself don't wait on someone
else to encourage you like Dame Dash
told me be your own superhero that's
really powerful um because a lot of
times people aren't clapping for you or
then there's those who are clapping for
you and really hope you lose and it's
all fake you know and then they'll clap
for you in front of other people but
when it's just you and them they're not
doing the same they're really like not
even supportive in any kind of way you
know you deal with stuff like
that I totally understand so um we have
reached the hold on one second here
we've reached the end of our
interview and uh hold on one oh no they
won't allow me to do this so but we we
reached round two which is pretty short
this is the lightning
round uh I don't got the effects yet but
I'm working on
that but um so the lightning round um
what do you like to do talk talking or
texting
texting yes and favorite day of the week
oh favorite day of the
week uh
Sunday Sunday it's the first day of the
week awesome uh favorite city in the US
besides the one that you live in
right I guess it's
C uh
SAC oh say that one more time you said
yeah I can hear you there there's there
seems be a delay for the rest of the
week okay okay okay okay and then
Sacramento is your favorite
City awesome and nickname your parents
used to call
you my parents
yeah uh when I was little
yeah that's a question what did they
used to call
me um well my grandparents to say my
baby my
baby my baby my
baby
uh uh would you rather be able to speak
every language of the world or be able
to talk to
animals speak every language in the
world awesome favorite
holiday uh no
I don't have one I'm I am with you on
that one I'm I'm zero too um how long
does it take for you to get
ready uh depends where am I
going so is it like 30 minutes if you're
just going out to the store and then
five gajillion minutes uh uh when you
are going out to party or oh no you
don't party but you know like how long
like what's the longest it takes you to
get
ready probably an hour and 15
minutes hour and 15 minutes that's long
yeah yeah cause I I'm in a shower I have
a a really beautiful shower head that
changes colors it's kind of
mesing and then I pray and I listen to
my music so I'm having a mini
concert and I'm just like zoning out you
know daydreaming so I'll be like my gosh
I been here my my fingers are wrinkle
let me get
out awesome okay so a few more questions
so um Michael Jackson or
Prince Michael Jackson oh my gosh I used
to be obsessed with Michael Jackson when
I was little oh my goodness he was like
my dad actually my dad when I was
younger everybody El just say oh my gosh
your dad is so fine he looks like a mix
of Michael and
Prince cu Jerry Cur and
everything yeah Michael like I was a fan
of Michael I was obsessed when I was a
kid my M like it actually my mom was
obsessed with Michael she passed that
down because she had all her all his
records and then I was the New Age
Michael so I I liked him and then my son
liked Michael uh when he was growing up
so he used to do the D like I used to
put him on on camera because he'd be
doing all the Michael Jackson moves and
everything so yeah like Michael is
straight up uh
you know he's Universal so um what age
you want to
retire uh retire from the sports from
anything like don't want to work
anymore
retired uh 50 50 and invisib
invisibility or super strength which
superhero power would you like
super strength super strength and the
last question is it wrong for
vegetarians to eat animal
crackers uh depends is the is the animal
crackers have
dairan oh no you said vegetarian
vegetarian oh not
vegan vegetarian oh no it's only in the
shape of an animal yes but then I guess
it depends on their own guilt and their
own own conscience because it might feel
guilty so then it depend it depends on
the person and depends on the person
yeah awesome well thank you so much lar
for coming into the hustle Zone we got
one more thing that you have to do so
I'm going to do a call and response and
then um so I'm gonna say welcome to the
and I need you to scream hustle Zone as
loud as you can but this time um this
will be the first time where I'm G to
ask you to um Say gang gang at the end
because you did that for our video and
everyone was like who is this
chick I was like that that was that was
awesome but anyway so I'm gonna say
welcome to the hustle Zone and then you
know you could say gang gang at the
end okay you ready okay welcome to the
hustle
Zone yes
awesome thank you so much the star um I
heart you I'm like a fan of a fan I'm a
fan fan fan because um it's just oh so
it's amazing honest like when I when
like you first sent me the video and I
saw you I was just I was replaying the
video over and over again I'm like how's
she running so fast and then I go
through your this just the energy that
you have the positive energy that you're
giving off to everyone that's around you
and then when you put the music on and
you just you feeling yourself but you're
like you know I'm just staying on my
grind I just I love it all and I'm so
you know it's a pleasure it was it was
an honor to to to have you on because I
know you're gonna blow up and I'm gonna
be one of those people be like yeah I
know the star she was on my she was on
my
show thank you so much I really
appreciate you yeah hustle on is amazing
you guys are very very I say different
than other outlets you're you're you
care and it's not just to build yourself
up but it's like you want to show that
you care and be a part of other people's
lives and I think that's amazing and I
hope you guys go far and blow just the
same yeah well thank you so much and
we'll see each other at the top because
you know with hustle zone I'm trying not
to give the te because you know what it
was so funny I was watching um I was
watching uh this like some of these
these these bloggers they'll have videos
on YouTube and they they always spill
the tea and um you know and I'm looking
for ideas and just looking for what's
current and whatever and then one girl
was just getting off how she was like
you know how do this how come this black
celebs don't ever stop at the black
media Outlets like they always get past
us I'm like well uh for one thing stop
it like you guys keep on spilling the
tea like we don't want to be the ones
spilling the tea yeah we'll mention
certain things there'll be like certain
posts that we'll be opinionated about of
course but we don't spill people's
personal drama we try to keep that stuff
out and we're trying to build up our
community but also you know keep it
entertaining so like you know we're
hoping that hustle Zone can be known for
just being you know you be able to get
your entertainment content but not have
to be up in people's business right
because like let's say you get famous
right and then you're dating you know
some big basketball player or whatever
right like you don't what you know we're
not going to be spilling no tea like
it's it's not fair it's not fair to us
there's there's so much of us and the
media constantly is tearing black people
down so we're hoping you know in the
future that you know we could be that
outlet where you know we build people up
but also not be too boring you know what
I mean like keep a little bit
exciting just just just a little bit
exciting but anyway much love to you and
um and hopefully uh uh um and when do
you try out for the
um do
it awesome um tell me when are you
trying out for the Olympics and how does
that all go down before you go
um well I plan to be trying out in
April oh and then and this will be for
the Olympics in when's the Olympics for
you uh well okay so now that I'm doing
two sports so I have whole new goals now
uh track cycling uh that will be 2024
because a lot of people are like oh what
about this year which is 2020 but I'm
like uh different thing about uh cycling
they um qualified two years out so they
qualified two years ago and that I
wasn't in a sport then I just I'm a
newborn now so that's the plan on 20
shooting for 2024 now with that and then
2022 for the winner so I'm plan on
winter and summer wow wow well keep us
updated and when you hit any big
milestones and you want us to promote it
or you want to get on camera and talk
about it just let me know um you're
forever going to be in our hearts and
we'll um whatever we could do to help
you get a help bring awareness we'll do
it thank you so much I really appreciate
you I don't take it for granted thank
you so much much love and I will talk to
you
later all right definitely okay peace
so um wow what an amazing interview she
is definitely like you know Dame Dash is
saying that she's a uh you know to be
her own superhero but she that by that
story alone she's everybody's superhero
I think that if you're not following lar
you guys need to call you need to follow
her it's lar Olympic girl on on
Instagram U if you guys see her if you
see the footage the footage is amazing
um I've never seen anyone run like that
she's she's I think she's faster than
Hussein Bol that's what I think I think
she's like you know we just what we we
what we can't do is we cannot bring any
Kryptonite around her because we don't
want her to die she's that she is that
Superhero is you know what I mean like
she will die from Kryptonite you know I
seen her fly I seen thear fly
I I se her like lift up a car to help a
baby she is that she is that athletic I
mean it it just blows your mind and and
and when you see her you're going to be
a fan of her too you're going to hear
about her um and you heard it here on
the hustle Zone you know she's going to
she's going to rock the whole world and
I believe it so and you know for for all
the stuff that she's been through I
think that this is even that much more
important because we need to show young
women and young men it doesn't matter
what your life throws you your way you
can get out and you can make something
happen so um this was a special hustle
Zone today I'm so glad to have her as a
guest and you know you guys can check us
out on go live and
prosper uh blah
blah Apple music uh
Spotify uh Stitcher at Google podcast
you can check us out on any of those
mediums you can check us out of course
at hustle Zone TV and at hustle Zone and
also follow us at B creative um so
that's b w t k r a t i or k r a
TI um uh follow us on Instagram if
you're looking for marketing services so
I love you guys from the B bottom of my
heart and I will talk to you guys later
peace